ZUZANA TOMČÍK

Data Analyst / BI Consultant

4 +420 775 654 362

@ www.linkedin.com/in/zuzana-tomcik

@ Zuzana.Tomcik91@gmail.com

Prague, Czech Republic



SUMMARY

Following my parental leave, I'm returning to the workforce with a renewed focus on transitioning into the field of data analysis. With experience in project management, financial analysis, and IT projects coordination, I'm also a certified Data Analyst. My goal is to use these skills to make data-driven decisions and improve business performance. In my experiences, both as a student and at work, I've earned academic awards for research, excelled in team management, and been recognized for leading project.

EXPERIENCE

IT Network Analyst

Accenture Central Europe B.V.

Global professional services with leading capabilities in digital, cloud and security

- Supported 3 project teams by keeping project documentation updated and providing client updates - utilized data visualization to produce various project schedules and reports.
- Documenting and identification items and decisions during meetings with company leaders. Maintaining and updating internal systems for time tracking, attendance, and billing.
- As of now parental leave.
- Technology used: MS Office (Excel, PowerPoint), CRM, Atlassian's products -Jira and Confluence, Slack, Discord.

Lead Project Implementation Manager

AT&T Global Network Services Slovakia, s.r.o.

iii 12/2017 - 12/2019 ♀ Bratislava

An American provider of telecommunications, media, and technology services

- Managed end-to-end implementation and lifecycle of the biggest client high visibility, daily reporting with directors, techs and VP.
- Helped with testing and documenting processes, contributing over 150 overtime hours. Data collection via Power BI reports and internal systems, providing updates about the project status. Issue tracking, reporting and with tech team providing fixing and resolution on daily basis.
- Led a team of 5 and achieving recognition with the Above and Beyond certificate for exceptional performance.
- Part of various volunteering programs and internal teams such as Spirit team, Fun team. Education team.
- Technology used: MS Excel, Power BI, MS PowerPoint, internal systems.

Finance Specialist / Relocation Specialist

Santa Fe Relocation Services

m 01/2016 - 11/2017

Slovakia/Austria area

Global mobility company specializing in high-quality relocation services

- Processing and preparing financial and business forms, facilitating purchases, performing routine calculations to produce statistical analyses and reports.
- Managed individual accounts, adhered to department budgets, and audited financial statements - maintained records and communicated with financial
- Ensuring data accuracy in financial spreadsheets managed project scheduling, budgeting, and reporting, ensuring profitability for each relocation.
- Technology used: MS Office (Excel, PowerPoint, Word), internal CRM system.

SKILLS

Data analysis Power BI **Tableau**

MS EXCEL PYTHON SQL ETL

Quantitative and qualitative analysis

Delivery project management

Problem-solving Communication skills

Reporting

STRENGTHS



A fast and eager learner

Strong enthusiasm for continuous learning, self-improvement and rapid adaptation to new challenges.



Leadership and Team Management

Led a team of 5 members across 4 nationalities, successfully delivering the biggest customer project.

ACHIEVEMENTS



Academic and Research Excellence

Received several Rector's Awards for excellence in academia and research, significantly contributing to the field of criminal intelligence analyses and tax evasion detection.



Leadership in Project Management

Managed project implementation the biggest client at AT&T (10k+ sites), demonstrating leadership and project management prowess.



Volunteering and Community Service

Actively participated in various volunteering programs, demonstrating a strong commitment to community service and organizational contribution.

EDUCATION

Master of Security-Legal Protection of Persons and Property

Academy of Police Force

Bachelor of International Economic Relations

University of Economics

AWARDS

2014, 2016 | 1st place in Student scientific research

1st place for the best student and scientific research activity under the section "Police Sciences" - April 2014 and 2016 (topics: New Software tools used in criminal intelligence analyzes, Tax evasions - manifestation and detection possibilitites). Slovak and international (CZ-SK) round at Academy of Police Force in Bratislava and Prague

2018 | AT&T Above and Beyond award

From AT&T Director of Global Services: "For stepping up and taking overall responsibility for customer and even though I do realize you had "big shoes to fill" you have flawlessly taken over and continued our efforts to deliver."

LANGUAGES

English

B2

PUBLICATIONS

Detection of Tax Evasion and Taxrelated Criminal Activity

Friedrich Ebert Stiftung Representation in the Slovak Republic, Academy of Police Force in Bratislava

prof. Ing. Jozef Stieranka, PhD., Maj. Ing. Marianna Presperínová, PhD., MBA; Bc. Zuzana Zahuráková,

Scientific study from the empirical part of the scientific research task registered at the Police Academy in Bratislava No. 164 - quantitative and qualitative analysis of tax evasions.

TRAINING / COURSES

Data Analyst certification

Coders Lab IT Academy

11/2023 - 05/2024

Full

time coding bootcamp. The course contains 193 hours of classes with tutors and prepares for Data analyst position. Scope: Excel, Python, SQL, Data visualization